If you want to edit one of your projects in general,
you must first select the one you want to modify.
The selected project becomes highlighted
and its contents are displayed on the right side.
Use the "Edit project" button located on the right to start your editing process.
In this interface you can create different folders to structure your data package
by using the "Add folder" button.
In the pop-up window that appears after using the button,
you can enter a name for the new folder.
Then click on the Create folder button.
Now, if you want to put your data in this newly created folder,
you just have to select it and it will open.
You can add as many folders as you need.
If you don’t need a folder anymore, you can delete it by using the recycle bin symbol.
When you click on the symbol, a dialogue box will offer you two options.
You can either leave the folder unchanged.
Or you can permanently delete the selected folder.
Please note that if you delete a folder,
all the data contained in that folder will also be deleted.